- [Man] Women, you don't
have that kinda knowledge.
You understand?
Look at that, look
Hoo.
Now that is foxy.
You can do other girls, but
you couldn't do nothing.
Look at, what is he doing?
I thought I told him to go home.
What is he doing?
Look at, she going pass him up.
Back up.
(Laughs)
Look at you.
- Hey!
(snapping)
♪- You knocked me for my feet, now baby ♪
♪ Hoo ♪
♪ Hee hee ♪
♪ Go on girl ♪
♪ Ow ♪
♪ Hee ♪
♪ Hey pretty baby with the high heels on ♪
♪ You give me fever like
I've never, ever known ♪
♪ You're just a product of loveliness ♪
♪ I like the groove of your
walk, your talk, your dress ♪
♪ I feel your fever from miles around ♪
♪ I'll pick you up in my car
and we'll paint the town ♪
♪ Just kiss me baby and tell me twice ♪
♪ That you're the one for me ♪
♪ The way you make me feel ♪
♪ [Chorus]- The way you make me feel ♪
♪ - You really turn me on ♪
♪ [Chorus]- You really turn me on ♪
♪ - You knock me off of my feet ♪
♪ [Chorus]- You knock me off of my feet ♪
♪ - My lonely days are gone ♪
♪ [Chorus]- My lonely days are gone ♪
♪ - I like the feelin' you're givin' me ♪
♪ Just hold me, baby, and I'm in ecstasy ♪
♪ Oh, I'll be workin' from nine to five ♪
♪ To buy you things to
keep you by my side ♪
♪ I never felt so in love before ♪
♪ Just promise, baby,
you'll love me forevermore ♪
♪ I swear I'm keepin' you satisfied ♪
♪ 'Cause you're the one for me ♪
♪ The way you make me feel ♪
♪ [Chorus]- The way you make me feel ♪
♪-You really turn me on ♪
♪ [Chorus]- You really turn me on ♪
♪ - You knock me off
of my feet now, baby ♪
♪ [Chorus]- You knock me off of my feet ♪
♪ - My lonely days are gone ♪
♪ [Chorus]- My lonely days are gone ♪
♪ - Go on, girl! ♪
♪ Go on! ♪
♪ Hee hee ♪
♪ Ow ♪
♪ Go on, girl! ♪
♪ I never felt so in love before ♪
♪ Promise, baby, you'll
love me forevermore ♪
♪ I swear I'm keepin' you satisfied ♪
♪ 'Cause you're the one for me ♪
♪ The way you make me feel ♪
♪ [Chorus]- The way you make me feel ♪
♪ - You really turn me on ♪
♪ [Chorus]- You really turn me on ♪
♪ - You knock me off
of my feet now, baby ♪
♪ [Chorus]- You knock me off of my feet ♪
♪ - My lonely days are gone ♪
♪ [Chorus]- My lonely days are gone ♪
♪ - The way you make me feel ♪
♪ [Chorus]- The way you make me feel ♪
♪ - You really turn me on ♪
♪ [Chorus]- You really turn me on ♪
♪ - You knock me off
of my feet now, baby ♪
♪ [Chorus]- You knock me off of my feet ♪
♪ - My lonely days are gone ♪
♪ [Chorus]- My lonely days are gone ♪
♪ - Ain't nobody's business ♪
♪ [Chorus]-The way you make me feel ♪
♪ Ain't nobody's business ♪
♪ [Chorus]- You really turn me on ♪
♪ - Ain't nobody's business
but mine and my baby ♪
♪ [Chorus]- You knock me off of my feet ♪
♪ Ooh! ♪
♪ [Chorus]-My lonely days are gone ♪
♪ -Give it to me ♪
♪ [Chorus]- The way you make me feel ♪
♪ -Give me some time ♪
♪ Come on, be my girl ♪
♪ [Chorus]- You really turn me on ♪
♪ - I want you to be mine ♪
♪ Ain't nobody's business ♪
♪ [Chorus]- You knock me off of my feet ♪
♪ - Ain't nobody's business
but mine and my baby ♪
♪ [Chorus]- My lonely days are gone ♪
(snapping)
- How you doing, man?
(Intense music)
♪-Oh ♪
♪ [Chorus]- The way you make me feel ♪
♪ - Oh ♪
♪ [Chorus]- You really turn me on ♪
♪ You knock me off of my feet ♪
♪ My lonely days are gone ♪
(water spraying)